<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Komodian - Komodian is a community-led marketing effort for Komodo Platform ecosystem projects</title>
    <link>https://komodian.org/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Komodian - Komodian is a community-led marketing effort for Komodo Platform ecosystem projects</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://komodian.org/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chips</title>
      <link>https://komodian.org/projects/chips/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://komodian.org/projects/chips/</guid>
      <description>About Chips CHIPS is a decentralized adopatable gaming platform that meet the needs of any card game and predictable betting scenarios.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hempcoin</title>
      <link>https://komodian.org/projects/hempcoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://komodian.org/projects/hempcoin/</guid>
      <description>About Hempcoin The HempCoin ($THC) was one of the first 30 cryptocurrencies founded in 2014.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Komodo Platform</title>
      <link>https://komodian.org/projects/komodo-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://komodian.org/projects/komodo-platform/</guid>
      <description>About Komodo Platform Useful links Awesome Komodo Wallets AtomicDEX Resources MarketMaker KMD Explorers Code Libraries C++ C Java Rust Golang JavaScript C# Proof of Concept Apps General CC Assets Channels Coda Dice Dilithium Faucet Games Gateways Heir Marmara MoMoM Musig Oracles Payments Pegs Prices Rewards Rogue Sudoku Tetris Chat Documentation User Documentation Developer Documentation Knowledgebase and Help Ecosystem Projects Veruscoin Maramara Pirate Utrum KMDice (Stalled) HyperDEX Chainswap Coque BitcoinHush KMDLabs Ecosystem Companies/Organisations ChainMakers ChainZilla Komodo Pioneers Peer2Cloud Pungo PearlPay RedFox AXO DEX Stats dPoW (delayed Proof of Work) Secured Projects Hush GameCredits Chips Einsteinium Articles mentioning Komodo Videos mentioning komodo Resources Conferences Meetups E-Books Twitter Website Wallets Official Komodo Wallets Website: https://komodoplatform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tokel Platform</title>
      <link>https://komodian.org/projects/tokel-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://komodian.org/projects/tokel-platform/</guid>
      <description>About Tokel Platform Tokel is a dedicated token and non-fungible token (NFT) platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Verus Coin</title>
      <link>https://komodian.org/projects/veruscoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://komodian.org/projects/veruscoin/</guid>
      <description>About Veruscoin Verus Coin aims to be the world&amp;rsquo;s most advanced technology, zero knowledge privacy-enabling blockchain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pirate Chain</title>
      <link>https://komodian.org/projects/pirate-chain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://komodian.org/projects/pirate-chain/</guid>
      <description>About Pirate Chain Launched in 2018 with the primary goal of being the most private and secure digital currency, Pirate Chain strives to protect the financial privacy of every user in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marmara Credit Loops</title>
      <link>https://komodian.org/projects/marmara/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://komodian.org/projects/marmara/</guid>
      <description>About Marmara Credit Loops Marmara Chain started as a joint project between Marmara University Open Innovations Lab and Komodo Platform Technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Collider</title>
      <link>https://komodian.org/projects/crypto-collider/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://komodian.org/projects/crypto-collider/</guid>
      <description>About Crypto Collider Useful links Website :https://cryptocollider.com/
Blog: https://www.publish0x.com/crypto-collider/
Explorer: https://clc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SmartFi</title>
      <link>https://komodian.org/projects/smartfi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://komodian.org/projects/smartfi/</guid>
      <description>About SmartFi SmartFi is a unique monetary system. It combines monetary policy with the freedoms of cryptocurrency to create a self-sustaining open-lending platform, providing the holders of SmartFi Token the opportunity to manage the system and become the beneficiaries of the wealth creation that would otherwise accrue to traditional banks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
